buygames.ps 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy | BuyGames.PS

#### PRIVACY POLICY

The private enterprise  (collectively, the "BuyGames.PS") respect your privacy rights and recognize the importance of protecting the Personal Information (as defined below) provided by you to us. This Privacy Policy describes how the Company collects, stores, and uses the Personal Information you provide to us through the Company's web sites and through telephone or e-mail communications you may have with us. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding the Company's use of the Personal Information you provide to us, and the actions you can take to access this information and request that the Company correct or delete it. Subscribed in the data protection registry with number: 22620

#### CONSENT

By using the Company's web sites, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and you consent to the practices described herein with respect to the Company's collection, use and disclosure the Personal Information provided by you to us. This is the Company's entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy in accordance with the terms herein at any time, which is why we encourage you to visit this page often, review this Privacy Policy frequently, and remain informed about any changes to it.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

"Personal Information" means information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. On all Company web sites that collect Personal Information, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product, service, or feature you have requested. We collect Personal Information when you contact us, when you register with us, when you use our products and services, when you submit an order with us, when you visit our web sites or the web sites of certain of the Company's partners, and when you enter promotions and sweepstakes.

#### NEWSLETTERS

If you wish to subscribe to the Company's newsletter(s), we will use your name and e-mail address to send the newsletters to you.

#### OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTED

Some information may be collected automatically every time you visit the Company's web sites, such as cookies and computer information. In addition, information may be collected from other independent, third-party sources. We also collect information about which pages you visit within this site. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique URL.

#### COOKIES

The Company uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies as part of its interaction with your browser. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier (a file) that the Company's web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive through a web browser to enable its systems to recognize your browser for record-keeping purposes. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser, while a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our web sites. We use persistent cookies to identify and track which sections of its web site you most often visit. We also use persistent cookies in areas of its web site where you must register, and where you are able to customize the information you see, so that you don’t have to enter your preferences more than once.

Some of the Company's business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on the site. We have no access to or control over these cookies (see ‘Third Party Advertising’ and ‘Third Party Cookies’ below). Accordingly, this Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Company only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### LOG FILES

As is true of most web sites, the Company gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet services provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. The Company uses this information to analyze trends, to screen for fraud, to administer the Company's sites, to track user’s movements around the web sites and to gather demographic information about the Company’s user base as a whole.

#### INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTY SOURCES

To improve services and enhance personalization, the Company may periodically obtain information about you from other independent third party sources and add it to our account information. For example, when you visit a site on which the Company advertises, and click through such advertisement, the Company may place cookies on your computer.

#### USE OF INFORMATION

The Company collects Personal Information to verify the accuracy of your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date provided, to screen for fraud, to bill you for products and services purchased and to pay you for products and services sold. The Company uses your e-mail address(es) to contact you regarding the status of your order when necessary and to send you a Receipt Purchase/Sale Confirmation and Order Shipping Notification.

#### SECURITY

The Company protects the privacy and integrity of the information it collects by employing appropriate administrative protocols, technical safeguards, and physical security controls designed to limit access, detect and prevent the unauthorized access, improper disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the information under its control. The Company transmits the information used by its external service providers for the specific outsourced operations listed above across public and private networks via recognized encryption technologies, such as by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. Although the Company follows the procedures set forth above to protect the Personal Information submitted to the Company, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Thus, while the Company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, the Company cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### INTERNET FRAUD

The Company has a ZERO TOLERANCE policy for Internet fraud or any attempt to access or acquire customer or other information on its web sites via illegal or surreptitious means. The Company works with local, national, and international fraud investigation agencies and employs a variety of electronic and other means to discourage, detect, and intercept fraudulent activities. The Company aggressively prosecutes, to the fullest extent of the law, those perpetrators apprehended conducting fraudulent activities on its web site. Agencies with which the Company cooperates are: state and local police authorities, the United States Federal Bureau of Investigation, US and International Customs Agencies, and Interpol.

#### CHILDREN

The Company's sites are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. The Company does not buy or sell products or services from or to children. Any person who provides their information to the Company through the Company's web sites represents to the Company that they are 18 years of age or older.

#### CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

The Company will from time-to-time update this Privacy Policy, each time revising the last updated date at the top of the Privacy Policy and indicate the nature of the revisions within the statement. The Company will notify customers of material changes to this statement by e-mail or by placing prominent notice on its web site.
